>> Brian Holt: 实际上要给你看一个很酷的魔术，这个包裹可以为你做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Actually gonna show you
a cool trick that parcel can do for you.
因此，我们需要安装新的客户机库以针对 API 发出请求。
So, we need to install a new client
library to make requests against an API.
> > Brian Holt: 那么，我要在这里做什么，我要说，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
what I'm gonna do here, I'm gonna say,
导入， >> Brian Holt: 如下所示的 ANIMALS
import,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: ANIMALS like this from
@frontendmasters， >> Brian Holt: /pet 类似。
@frontendmasters,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: /pet like that.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，你和我没有安装这个，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, you and
I have not installed this, right?
这不在我们的包里，但是包裹够聪明的说，哎，
This was not in our package.json, but
parcel is smart enough to say, hey,
就在 NPM 注册中心我去帮你拿
this is out on the NPM registry,
I'll just go grab it for you.
所以你不需要在 NPM 上安装它，它会为你做。
So you don't have to NPM install it,
it'll just do it for you.
如果你看这里我说省省吧
So if you see here, if I say save,
它会说在那里安装前面的主人/宠物
it's gonna say Installing
frontendmasters/pet right there.
>> Brian Holt: 在安装时，它将重建项目，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And, while it's installing,
it will rebuild the project, and
现在我们可以在一个项目上找到它
now it's available to us on a project.
好了我们安装了这个主子/宠物
Okay, so
we installed this frontendmasters/pet.
如果您感到更舒适，那么只能说 npm install @frontendmasters/pet。
If you feel more comfortable, you can just
say npm install @frontendmasters/pet.
>> Brian Holt: 但您也可以为
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
you can also have parcel just do it for
他是你的一个有趣的特征
him which is kind of a fun
feature that it does for you.
> > Brian Holt: 再次，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And, again,
如果您查看 package.json ，您可以看到它已安装它。
if you look in package.json you
can see that it installed it.
这里，前面的主人/宠物，在他们的森林里保存。
Here, frontrendmasters/pet and
save that in their forest.
>> Brian Holt: Magical.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Magical.
>> Brian Holt: 好的
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
现在我们有了这个 ANIMAL 的阵列，它只是我相信的一系列的字符串。
now we have this ANIMAL's array which
is just an array of strings I believe.
布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 在这里，我们会说动物，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here,
we're gonna say const animal,
设置动物 = useState 和
set animal = useState and
我们要从一只狗开始， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
we're gonna start with a dog,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then
we're gonna go down and
然后我们就会在我们的输入下面还有一个标签
then we are going to make underneath
our input there, another label,
>> Brian Holt: htmlFor = 动物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: htmlFor = animal.
> > Brian Holt: 在这个过程中，我们将选择动物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And inside of that,
we're going to select Animal.
> > Brian Holt: 我们将在其中进行选择。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And,
we're gonna put a select inside of that.
所以选择， >> Brian Holt: id="动物"，
So select,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: id="animal",
>> Brian Holt: value= 动物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: value= animal.
>> Brian Holt: onChange = e，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: onChange = e, and
then setAnimal e.target.value。
then setAnimal e.target.value.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以我要给你看一些很酷的东西
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I'm gonna show you
something pretty cool that we've
已经完成了
done already.
所以说，嘿，如果你要做 " onChange" ，
So it's saying, hey,
if you're gonna do onChange,
我需要你也有伦布卢
I need you to have onBlur as well.
因为一些屏幕阅读器，当你在做东西的时候，
Because some screen readers,
when you're tabbing across things,
不触发 onChange 事件。
don't trigger onChange events.
这意味着当与屏幕朗读器一起使用时，代码将无法工作，
Which means that your code would not work
when being used with a screen reader,
这显然是个大派对对吧
which is obviously a big party foul,
right?
我喜欢 jsx 的盟友只为你和你
And I love the jsx ally,
just catches up for you and
说我不会让你前进直到你解决这个问题的对吧
says like I'm not gonna let you go
forward until you fix this, right?
很明显这让人分心来看这么多红线
Obviously like, this is so
distracting to see so many red lines,
我自己都应付不来对吧
I just can't even handle myself, right?
所以，我们可以通过说 onblur = e 来解决，
So, we can fix that by saying onBlur = e,
setAnimal， >> Brian Holt: e.target.value，
setAnimal,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: e.target.value,
啊，对吧 ?
as well, right?
现在一切都很开心我们已经确定了我们的无障碍环境
And now, it's all happy again
cuz we fixed our accessibility
问题， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
issue,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
然后我们会在这里放一堆不同类型的
And then we're gonna put a bunch of
options in here of different types of
我们可以寻找的动物
animals that we can search for.
第一个，我们放在这里，只是一个空白的选项。
So the first one, we put in here,
is just a blank option.
这意味着当我们搜索所有动物的时候，对吗 ?
This is gonna represent when we search for
all animals, right?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我想你也可以放进来
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I guess you
could put in here as well,
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Something like this,
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And put All as well.
这可能不是个坏主意
That's probably not a bad idea.
> > Brian Holt: 然后在这里，我们要做花括号
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here,
we're gonna do curly braces and
我们这里有一组动物对吧
we have an array of animals here, right?
我们要对每个动物都有一个选择
And we wanna have one option for
every animal in there.
>> Brian Holt: 我们有一个字符串列表，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
what we have is a list of strings, and
我们需要的是一份组件清单对吧
what we need back from it is
a list of components, right?
有道理吗
It makes sense?
我们有一系列的字符串和
Like, we have a list of strings and
我们想把这些字符串的清单变成一个选项列表
we wanna turn those list of strings
into a list of option components.
也可以选择选项卡或任何您要调用的选项卡。
Or option tabs or
whatever you want to call them.
> > Brian Holt: 好，幸运的是，有些东西直接构建成 JavaScript
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well, luckily, there’s
something built directly into JavaScript
将一系列事物转化为另一种事物，对，
that translates one array of things to
another array of things, right, and
这叫做地图
it’s called map.
> > Brian Holt: 因此，如果我说动画 . 映射，对， cut 它是一个数组，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So if I say animas.map,
right, cuz it’s an array,
然后你给它一个在这个阵列中的一个项目
then you give it a function that
takes an item in that array and
把它变成别的东西
transforms it into something else.
所以我要拿这个串好吗
So I'm gonna take this string, right?
或者，我们只称它为动物，因为它就是这样。
Or, we'll just call it animal
because that's what it is.
>> Brian Holt: 然后，我们将在选项中选择该退货
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're
gonna have that return in option
组件， >> Brian Holt: 使用值
component,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: With the value of
这个选择成分将会成为动物
that option component is
going to be the animal.
而且，它也会展示动物。
And, also that it's
going to display animal.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，这里会有一条红线
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
it'll get a red line here for
只要一会儿我们就能解决了
just a second which we'll
fix in just one moment.
>> Brian Holt: 这是否有意义 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So does this make sense?
首先， >> Brian Holt: 通过箭头函数，
First of all,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: With arrow functions,
你可以让他们含蓄的对吧
you could have them implicit returned,
right?
所以在这个特殊的情况下，我有箭的功能，没有花括号，
So in this particular case, I had the
arrow function and I have no curly braces,
这就意味着它隐含地回归了
which means it’s implicitly returned.
因此，如果我删除了此括号并删除了此括号，那么这将是等价的。
So this would be equivalent if I deleted
this parentheses and deleted this one.
> > Brian Holt: 我说了回来， >> Brian Holt: 就像这样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And I said return,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like that.
>> Brian Holt: 这两种情况相同，但
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Those two
things are the same, but
因为我有个括号在下一行继续，对，
because I have the parenthesis which
means continue on the next line, right,
那是隐含的回报
it's an implicit return.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
>> Brian Holt: 我给你们看的这两件事情完全一样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So those two things that
I showed you are exactly the same.
> > Brian Holt: 现在我要为每一个动物都有一个选择。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now I'm gonna
have one option for every animal.
> > Brian Holt: 当然，如果你回去看这里，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And indeed hopefully,
if you go back and look over here,
还不高兴，但是你可以看到， >> Brian Holt: 我有一份各种各样的
it's still upset but you can see,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I have a list of various
不同的选择
different options.
这只是个小一点
It's just a tiny bit bigger.
这里有个酒庄，鸟，猫，狗，马，兔子，鱼鳞翅，其他
So there's a barnyard, bird, cat, dog,
horse, rabbit, scales fins, other and
小火，就是可以搜寻的动物的类型
small furry, which are the type of
animals that can be able to search for
一个交叉 API。
a crosses API.